





PMP,ITIL,CSM,Program Manager seeking assignments in IT Program Management, Project Management, Stakeholder Management, Scrum Implementation, Digital Transformation, Shared Support Services, Cloud Migration, IT Strategic Planning, IT Infrastructure

Current Location: Kolkata

Total Experience: 17 Year(s) 0 Month(s) Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Hyderabad, Kolkata Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance Role: Program Mar

Industry: Oil and Gas/Power/Infrastructure/Energy

 $\label{thm:continuous} \textit{Key Skills: Program Manager}, \textit{IT Program Management}, \textit{Project Management}, \textit{Stakeholder Managemen$ Implementation, Digital Transformation, Shared Support Services, Cloud Mgration, IT Strategic Planning, Service

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Civil]

Transition,IT Infrastructure,PMP,ITIL,CSM Verified : Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21

Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

Worked as Project Control System Program Manager for Saipem Global Petroproject Services, Zurich currently in secondment duties in Jakarta taking care of Digital Transformation and cloud migration projects across south east Asia. Worked as Chief Technology Officer (CTO) for TECHVERITA taking care of Daily IT Operations, Infrastructure Delivery, Shared Support Services, IT Budgeting, IT Strategic Planning, Digital Transformation, Innovation, etc. Worked as a Cloud Mgration Program Manager for Multiple Clients across Europe for Internal IBM Cloud Ramp up program. Worked as Project Manager with IBM for a Norway based Client and is responsible for Citrix Farm Delivery with Dual-Leg (Cloud and Traditional) and Application Packaging & Deployment.

Work Experience

Saipem Global Petroprojects Services as Project Control System Program Manager-IT Sep 2019 to Sep 2020

Responsibility & Accomplishment:

Working as Project Control System Program Manager for Saipem Global Petroproject Services, Zurich currently in secondment duties in Jakarta taking care of Digital Transformation and doud migration projects across south east

Multiple System Development Project Monitoring and execution

AWS cloud migration of in-house Infrastructure.

Shared Support Services,

Planning

Stakeholder Management Scrum Implementation for Deliver

Digital Transformation

TECHVERITA as Chief Technology Officer (CTO)

Dec 2018 to Jun 2019

Working as Chief Technology Officer for TECHVERITA which includes RICE Education, Adamas University, Adamas International School, Adamas World School, Adamas Career, RICE IAS Academy, etc. Also working as Chief Technology Officer for Adams Digital Learning Private Limited, a RICE Group IT Services company.

Daily IT Operations. Infrastructure Delivery Shared Support Services IT Budgeting, IT Strategic Planning, Digital Transformation, Innovation

IBM as Senior Project Manager Mar 2016 to Nov 2018

Important

· Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

Responsibility & Accomplishments:

Worked as Senior Project Manager for Cloud Migration Factory catering projects across Europe and North America. Previously working as Transition and Transformation Project Manager for projects from UK, France, Norway, etc.

Working as Program Manager for WPP NAclient for consolidating all the datacenters into IBM Cloud Datacenter. Worked as a Senior Project Manager for a UK Treasury Clearance House Project facilitating the complete Built up of a New Cloud Data Center

Working as a Cloud Mgration Program Manager for Multiple Clients across Europe for Internal IBM Cloud Ramp up program.

Worked as a Service Transition Project Manager for a UK Based Client facilitating the complete service transition from ServiceNow to IBMICDS.

Worked as Project Manager with IBM for a Norway based Client and is responsible for Citrix Farm Delivery with Dual-Leg (Cloud and Traditional) and Application Packaging & Deployment.

Successful Remote Takeover of 300+ servers (Windows, Linux, AIX, ESX Farms with Oracle, SQL Databases running and their connected SAN) in countries like Brazil, Switzerland and Portugal.

Successful CMS. CMS4SAP and Traditional Relocation of Windows, Linux, AlX servers to IBM Managed Datacenter for LIK

Efficient Mgration using OVA as well as DT Methodology for Infrastructure servers catering the needs of AD, Jump Servers, etc.

Successful Upgrade of McAfee ePO Upgrade from 4.6 to 5.3 for entire Client Company.

Efficient LDAP Upgrade of 2000+ servers in extremely constrained timeline.

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E (Civil) from National Institute of Technology (Hamirpur, H.P) in 2003

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
AGILE	

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Bengali				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.